Guide to the Glenda Joe / Houston Asian American community advocacy and festival arts records, circa 1980-2015 MS 667
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Glenda Joe / Houston Asian American community advocacy and festival arts records
1980-2015
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Joe, Glenda
MS 667
24 Linear Feet 24 boxes
Records documenting the activities of Glenda Joe with the Houston Asian American Festival Association, as well as with community advocacy issues concerning the Asian American communities in Houston, circa 1980-2015.
Biographical / Historical
Glenda Joe is a Chinese-Irish-Texan business owner, activist, and Asian festival director. She was born in Houston in 1954, where the Joe family has lived for several generations after immigrating from China in 1882. Glenda organized her first civil rights rally at age 13 and has since been a prominent activist for the Asian-American community in Houston, serving as a consultant for Asian issues in the Houston Police Department, writing the Asian Merchant's Handbook to reduce interracial conflict in Asian-owned stores, and investigating hate crimes against Asians, to name a few. Her business, Great Wall Enterprises, is dedicated to helping Asian-Americans as well; it has done advertising and public awareness campaigns (raising awareness of immunizations, voting, the census) targeted to Asians, especially recent immigrants. In 1991, Glenda was the first Asian-American to run for Houston City Council; she also ran in 1993 but did lost both times. Glenda has also been a strong promoter of Asian arts in Houston. She first got involved in HAAFA in 1980 at age 26 and eventually became its executive director. She has led HAAFA in running the Houston Asian American Festival 1980-2007, Lunar New Year Houston 2008-present, the Asian Performing Arts Gala, and other cultural programs at Houston schools and universities. References: http://www.texashighways.com/culture-lifestyle/item/8268-extraordinary-texans-16 http://www.wbur.org/npr/195909643/tx2020-houston-racial-ethnic-diversity-americas-future
Biographical / Historical
The Houston Asian American Festival Association was founded in 1980 by Bill Joe (Glenda Joe's uncle), Bill & Eleanor Der Bing, Daniel & Akiko Watanabe, Dulal Datta, Phon Nguyen, CK Kim & Glenda Joe. In 1982, the project secured its formal nonprofit corporation status and has been led by various board members: Dr. Daniel Watanabe, Michael Chou, Yani Rose Keo, Rathna Kumar, Phan Duy, and Tony Joe Yeung. Glenda Joe has served as Executive Director. Its mission is to preserve, present and promote authentic Asian cultural arts in free admission annual events for the City of Houston. HAAFA has presented Houston's Asian American Festival (AAF) 1980-2007, and Lunar New Year Houston (LNYH) 2008-present. AAF and LNYH are pan-Asian celebrations, bringing together the performers, artists, and cuisines of many Asian countries including China, Japan, Vietnam, the Philippines, and the Pacific Islands. According to Glenda Joe: "HAAFA was organized in response to President Jimmy Carter's first proclamation of Asian Pacific American Heritage Week in 1980. It was the first time Asians from all ethnicities convened to work for common cause in Houston. It was the catalyst for pan-Asian organizing around other civic and social issues affecting all Asians in Houston." Between 1980 and 1985, venues for Houston's AAF were: Westbury Square, Sharpstown Center, Fonde Recreational Center. In 1985, Miller Theatre's general invited AAF to present pan-Asian arts annually. It was the first Asian cultural arts programming presented at Miller Theatre. It was the only pan Asian cultural arts presented on Miller Theatre stage until 1996. In 2006, Miller Theatre leadership changed. The new management, in a highly criticized action, singled out Houston's AAF for a "test case" for clearing out ethnic community arts from their annual schedule. While AAF lost its battle to present at Miler Theatre, AAF's legal protests and civic action precluded Miller Theatre from a wholesale ethnic cleansing of other small arts groups in its annual performance schedule. By 2007, appreciation and understanding of Asian cultural arts and the maturation of small arts groups mentored by AAF was a mission accomplished.
Scope and Contents
Records documenting the activities of Glenda Joe with the Houston Asian American Festival Association, as well as with community advocacy issues concerning the Asian American communities in Houston, circa 1980-2015.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research.
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please contact woodson@rice.edu for access and allow 24 hours retrieval time.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Glenda Joe, 2016.
Index Terms
Subjects
Theater; Asians -- America -- History; Music; Women
Document Types
slides (photographs); posters; videotapes; photographs; letters (correspondence); minutes (administrative records); clippings (information artifacts); reports
Places
Asian Americans; Art
Subjects (Persons)
Joe, Glenda
- Series I: HAAFA Business records
  - Asian American Festival News Clippings, 1980-1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Asian American Festival News Clippings, 2000-2007 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Asian American Festival programs, 1980-2008 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Asian Performing Arts Gala posters/programs other events, 1984-1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Asian Performing Arts Gala clippings, 1985-1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Festivals and events news clippings, 1985-1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Chinese and Korean-language news clippings, 1987-2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Sharpstown Senior High School - HAAFA event clippings + programs, 1989-1994 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - HAAFA / Glenda Joe news articles (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Politics (Miller Outdoor Theater admin and policies, govt funding for arts)- newsclippings, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - HAAFA: Texas Senate proclamation #1871, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Event planning documents - Lunar New Year Houston (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - HAAFA funding, Brown Foundation, 2005 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - HAAFA Funding MTAB open records request correspondence, 1992-2006-05-01 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - HAAFA general correspondence and kudos, 1994-2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - HAAFA performer bios and resumes (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - HAAFA TexAsia webpage screen captures, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Conflict with MTAB, clippings and correspondence, 2005-2007 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - MTAB/HAAFA correspondence and meeting transcript, 2005-2006 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - MTAB- annotated correspondence and meeting minutes, 2005-10-2005-12 (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - MTAB- audio cassettes, 2005-10-2005-12 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - HAAFA complaint against MTAB to HPD, 2006-12 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - MTAB open records request correspondence, 2006-12-2008-07 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - MTAB- Attorney's notes re HAAFA, 2006-01 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - MTAB articles of Inc. (1970) and amendments, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - HAAFA funding application to Miller Theatre, 2006 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - HAAFA MTAB open records, 2006-03-27-2006-04-26 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - HAAFA MTAB open records request, 2006-05-01 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - MTAB open records request, 2006-05-01 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Miller Theater- open records request, 2006-07-06 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - HAAFA packet for city council re MTAB, 2006-02 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - HAAFA/MTAB overview binder, see also appendices binders a-e (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - HAAFA/MTAB appendix binder a (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - HAAFA/MTAB appendix binder b (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - HAAFA/MTAB appendix binder c (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - HAAFA/MTAB appendix binder d (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - HAAFA/MTAB appendix binder e (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Series II: HAAFA Event video and film (Box 4)
  Scope and Contents
  Recordings of Lunar New Year Festival (2008) and Asian Festival (1981-1982) were sent for digitization, November, 2017, and are stored nearline with identifier numbers MS0667aip_001, MS0667aip_002, and MS0667aip_003. Original media from this group is stored in box 24. Not all tapes were able to be captured digitally. See spreadsheet printe in box 24.
  Additional recordings from box 4 are being sent for digitization in 2019. See spreadsheet printed in box 4.
  - Rathna Kumar Houston-Texas
    General
    1986 promo tape of Anjali Center for Performing Arts: students performing, Rathna Kumar teaching, interview with Kumar, educational segment on Indian dance
    VHS format
  - Rathna Kumar
    1986 promo tape of Anjali Center for Performing Arts- same footage as "Rathna Kumar Houston-Texas", maybe slightly longer edit?
  - Anjali Performing Arts Center
    Anjali students performing on stage.
  - Houston Asian American Association: thirteen stories, 1995-01-27-1995-01-31
    coverage from various Houston news channels of Chinese New Year celebrations, Asian American Festival at the Houston Zoo, Vietnamese/US relations and Vietnamese New Year, crime targeting Houston Asian community, Asian police officer recruitment.
  - Community close up - visions, 1999-09-25
    1 episode of ABC 13 series "Community CLose Up - Visions". Includes Martha Wong interview, coverage of Alliance for Multicultural Community Services and Asian American Festival (with interviews of Glenda Joe and Phan Duy).
  - Vietnamese music contemporary
    Woman doing tai chi outdoors with background music- sounds like Western music. Date unknown.
  - Phoenix outreach center documentary
    Documentary on Phoenix Outreach Center (provides counseling, education, food to youth in Houston 5th Ward). Produced by Yate's High School 11/12/94.
  - Phoenix outreach center
    6/8/96 KHOU report on Asian community supporting Phoenix Outreach Center- Asian businesses sponsoring a child, short interview with Glenda Joe.
  - Kaminari Taiko of Houston
    Audition tape of Japanese drumming group Kaminari Taiko: performances at Japan Festival 1997, Houston International Festival 1997.
  - Houston Korean Traditional Cultural Center
    Musical performances at Korean Traditional Cultural Center, Korean families eating in a cafeteria, award ceremony. Date unknown.
  - Sakura
    Sakura Dance Company performances: Asian American Festival 10/20/1990, Houston International Festival 1990, A World of Difference (festival?).
  - Asian Arts Houston Promo (3 copies)
    1987 promo tape of Asian Arts Houston: performances at Asian Arts Gala, advertises other programs AAH produces (exhibits, Asian American Festival, Chinese Shadow Theater).
  - Asian Arts Presentation 2:46 (2 copies)
    Asian Arts Houston promo: AAH runs Asian American Festival, Lunar New Year celebrations, Peace in the City. Date unknown.
  - Asian Festival
    Footage of 1994 Asian American Festival performances.
  - Asian Performing Arts Gala, 1988
    Video of entire (?) 1988 Gala performance.
  - Chinese New Year
    1/31/95 KHOU coverage of Chinese New Year celebrations, Glenda Joe interview on Asian businesses.
  - LNY sharpstown HS Asian Arts, 1990
    Lunar New Year performances at Sharpstown, presented by Asian Arts Houston.
  - Houston Young Artists' Concert
    1991. VHS format
  - Houston Young Artists' Concert, 1993
  - AAF Miller Eve. Prog., 1988
    Not working.
  - DEMO -Asian American Festival, 1988
    Video of AAF booths and performances.
  - Asian American Festival: local Houston coverage, 1992-10-21-1992-10-25
  - 10th Annual Asian American Festival Reel #1
    Access Houston channel- Houston Arts Express series coverage of AAF performances, interviews with Mitsi Shen and Danial Watanabe.
  - Asian Festival, 1996-10-18-1996-10-20
    Short reports from various news channels of AAF and people trying to build a new sports stadium near Chinatown.
  - Asian American Festival, 1997-10-17-1997-10-18
    Short reports/announcements of AAF on various news channels.
  - Asian American Festival, 1999-10-15-1999-10-17
    Short reports and announcements of AAF on various news channels.
  - Asian Festival: stories, 1993-09-28-1993-11-10
    Various news stories: Channel 2- Asian Cultures Month KHOU- AAF announcement, World Journal (Chinese language newspaper in US), Vietnam Vision (Vietnamese TV channel),bilingual signs, Glenda Joe and Martha Wong running for City Council ABC 13 and KPRC- Glenda Joe at corporate meeting advocationg for Asian community's needs
  - Vilma Santos
    English and Filipino language TV show- modern dancing. Includes dancer Jean Garcia's performance to "I'm Every Woman" by Whitney Houston- so must be sometime after 1992?
  - Changlu Wu's Solo Pipa Concert
    Jones Hall, date unknown.
  - King Lear part 1 (2 copies)
    Tape of Mandarin King Lear performance at Miller Theater during 16th Asian American Festival (1995).
  - King Lear part 2 (2 copies)
  - King Lear Whirlwind Art Group
  - Sharpstown Lunar New Year (2 copies)
    Both copies not working.
  - Son Nguyen
    Classical guitar performance in a church (?). Date unknown.
  - Unlabeled video of Asian Performing Arts Gala
  - Peace in the City
    3 news reports on Asian/black community interactions: conflict in LA and Houston, Glenda Joe's efforts to unite communities by founding Peace in the City, Sharpstown HS joint celebration of LNY and Black History Month. 2/17/94.
  - Video: Quan sun - New Year, Houston Asian American Festival, Tapes 1-6, 2008-02-28 (Box 24)
  - Video: 2nd Annual Asian Festival, and 3rd Annual Asian Festival at Sharpstown Center, 1981-05-31-1982-05-16 (Box 24)
  - Video: Kim Son, tapes 1-3, 2007-10-19 (Box 24)
  - External hard drive for items digitized from box 24 (Box 24)
    This material was processed into nearline digital objects with the identfiers MS0667aip_001, _002, and _003.
- Series III: HAAFA Photographs and slides
  - Artists,Taiwan and Vietnam
  - Asian American/ "fusion dance" - Asian American Dance Company (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Balinese Dancer (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Cambodian performance (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Chinese performance (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Dr. Chin:Chinese shadow puppetry (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - E. Chon (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Li Mei Hua and Mitsi Shen: Chinese dance schools and classical/ folkoric (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Filipino performances (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Indian performance (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Indonesian performances (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Japanese dance and taiko (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Korean dance (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - South Sea-Pacfic islander performances (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Taiwanese performances (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Thai performance (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Vietnamese performances (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Vietnamese lion dance (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Artists, Taiwan and Vietnam (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Martial arts/ Tai chi (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Artist Willy Wong (Chinese), 1980 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Festival crowds, booths, volunteer photos (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Glenda Joe and community leaders (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Houston Young Artists' Concert (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - HAAFA Production imagery/backdrops (Box 5, Folder 24-25)
  - AAF: Full show @ Wortham Theater (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Performance, unidentified (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Asian Arts Houston: Asian Performing Arts Gala (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Examples of Asian travel imagery (Box 5, Folder 29-30)
  - Negatives (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Festival held at Westbury Square, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Festival held at Sharpstown, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Festival held at Sharpstown Mall, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Festival held at Fonde recreation center, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Festival held at Fonde recreation center, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Festival held at Miller Outdoor Theatre, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Festival held at Miller Outdoor Theatre, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Performances, 1987-11 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Hearne Elementary performance, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Glenda Joe, images of (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Theresa Chang, images of (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Series IV: HAAFA recognitions and awards
  - Proclamation Asian American Festival Day, 1981-05-28 (Box 7)
  - The Vietnamese-American Youth Organization sincerely appreciates the Houston's Asian American Festival Association for its support as an associate sponsor of the Houston TET festival, 1995-02-04-1995-02-05 (Box 7)
  - Vietnamese American Youth Organization is very proud to have Houston's Asian Arts as a sponser of 1996 TET festival year of the rat, 1996-02-24-1996-02-25 (Box 7)
  - Vietnamese American Youth Organization is very proud to have Houston Asian American Festival Association as a sponsor of 6th annual TET Festival, 1997-02-08-1997-02-09 (Box 7)
  - Vietnamese American Youth Organization proudly presents Houston Asian-American Festival Association sponser of the 7th annual TET festival, 1998-02-01 (Box 7)
  - Vietnamese American Youth Organization proudly presents Houston Asian American Festival Association sponser of the 8th annual TET festival, 1999-02-21 (Box 7)
  - Houston's Asian American Festival Association sponser of the TET Festival, 2000-02-06 (Box 7)
  - Texas free-style Lion Dance championship judge master Ta Quoc Thinh TEX Asia Deep in the Heart of Asian Art Houston's Asian American Festival, 2007 (Box 7)
  - A Texas star for our star in recognition of a lifetime of advocacy and achivement in the arts TEX ASIA Deep in the Heart of Asian Art Houston's Asian American Festival salutes Mr. James Hong Houston 28th annual Asian American Festival, 2007-10 (Box 7)
  - Kay Bailey Hutchinson recognition of new year, 2008 (Box 7)
  - Proclamation office of the Mayor Sugar Land,Texas, 2008-02-24 (Box 7)
  - Anjali Center Performing Arts presented to Glenda Joe Houston Asian Arts on the occasion of the center's 33rd anniversary in grateful acknowledgement of your support, encouragement and help through the years, 2008-11-16 (Box 7)
  - Certificate of special congressional recognition presented to Houston Asian American Festival Association on the joyous occasion of your lunar new year festival, 2008-02-24 (Box 7)
  - The state of Texas resolution, 2008-02-24 (Box 7)
  - The state of Texas resolution, 2008-02-24 (Box 7)
  - Lunar new year Houston international celebration of the year of the rat, 2008-02-24 (Box 7)
  - The state of Texas resolution, 2013-02-10 (Box 7)
  - Certificate of special congressional recognition presented to Lunar New Year Houston on the occasion of your 2014 lunar new year celebration, 2014-02-09 (Box 7)
- Series V: Houston Police Department recruitment and complaints
  - HPD Asian recruitment/admission, cultural senstivity training, 1985-1997 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
  - Glenda's Joe agenda, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - HPD Police Advisory Committee- general info, meeting summaries (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - General HPD info, yearly reviews (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Al Lotz: extortion, 1987-1991 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Al Lotz: Hung Lam mug book case, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Al Lotz: Minh Suoi case, 1990-1996 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Al Lotz: Asian Task Force (Asian Squad), 1991-1998 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - AL Lotz: War against Council of Asian American Organizations, 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Al Lotz: Formal complaint and results, 1996-1997 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Tim Dang case, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Jim Strachan case, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Russell Dunlap (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Asian Community/ HPD town hall meeting documents, 1995-10-1996-02 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Asian crime (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Asian language hotline (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Formation of Asian squad (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Robbery/crime prevention in Asian community (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Summaries of dealings with HPD (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Grand Jury manual (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Series VI: Asian American community in Houston - census and demographics
  - First Houston Asian survey, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Census reports and notes, 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Minority settlement patterns reports, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Houston's ethnic communities (including Asian communities), 1996 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Census project, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Census project continued, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - GWE Census project:proposal, notes,correspondence, and news clippings, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Census news clippings, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Series VIII: Asian American community in Houston - advocacy issues
  - Race relations, esp. Asian/Black Houston + nationwide - racism, activism, and communication, 1982-1991 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - Redistricting, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Women's/ Asian women's activism, 1982-1996 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Asian businesses, 1982-2007 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Acres Homes boycott of Asian business, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - General Houston news, 1983-2002 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Informational brochures targeted to Asian immigrants, 1985-1993 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Asian Arts Houston: Arts in education projects, 1989-1993 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Pham family case, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Hung Truong murder, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Hung Nguyen case (Asian/ Black community conflict), 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - William Webber killing, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Asian Merchants Handbook, and letters requesting copies (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Asian merchants handbook translations, 1992-1993 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Glenda Joe personal clippings - city council (Box 13, Folder 16-17)
  - GKJ's speeches, press releases, 1995-1998 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Council of Asian American Organizations, proflie (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Series IX: Great Wall Communications records and television recordings
  - Subseries A: Correspondence and subject files
    - Commute Solutions/ mini pool advertising (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Air check advertising (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Texas Electric Choice (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Metro advertising (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Texas Commerce bank advertising (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Baby shots advertising (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Examples of various GWE advertising work (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Brochures (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Research on Houston Asian population (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - GWE references (qualifications,thank you letters) (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Great Wall resume (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - VoTexas clippings, correspondence (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - VoTexas advertising (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Subseries B: Television clips on videotape (VHS) (Box 15, Box 16)
    - Public utility commission of Texas video news release "Texas Electric Choice"
    - Mike/Glenda ch8, 1984-04-12
    - GJ ch11 Susie Wong and Laura/cheers, 1988-08-03
    - Women on the move, 1992-10-30
    - Asians in Houston,unity awards,and acres homes business awards, 1992-11-24-1993-02-26
    - Asian crime "city under seige" with Fran Fawcett and Carolyn Canville, 1994-04-11
    - Asian community, 1994-05-01
    - Asian violence, 1994-05-12
    - HPD Asian recruitment, 1994-05-22
    - GKJ city council, 1994-12-13
    - Glenda Joe on channel 8, 1992-05-01
    - Biracial kids, 1995-05-07-1995-05-09
    - Investigation, 1995-05-25
    - Ethics violations, 1995-06-26
    - RE: HPD Asian task force, 1995-08-12
    - Asian police officers, 1995-11-05
    - Baby shots commercial, 1995-11-16
    - Asian town hall meeting and cultural festival, 1996-02-01-1996-02-08
    - Houston rodeo scholarship, 1996-03-23-1996-03-25
    - Rodeo scholarship revoked, 1996-04-12-1996-04-15
    - Asian women's hotline,sexual harassment investigation and immigration reform, 1996-04-27-1996-05-02
    - Nightclubs sued by Vitetnamese, 1996-06-29-1996-06-30
    - Nightclubs sued by Vietnamese, 1996-06-29
    - HPD reaches out, 1996-07-10
    - HPD Recruiting, 1996-08-10
    - HPD compaints, 1996-09-04
    - Asian gangs, 1996-09-11
    - Asian politics, 1996-10-09
    - Racial discrimination case, 1996-12-14